{"data":[{"question":"Mary: \"I will play cards the day after tomorrow .\"     -> Mary informed me...................................","answer":"she would play cards after two days","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Sophie: \"I went to bed early last night\".     -> Sophie said ............................................","answer":"she had gone to bed early the previous night.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"\"You have to change this sentence into reported speech\" - the teacher said to Jenny.     -> The teacher told .............................................................","answer":"me I had to change that sentence into reported speech","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Lorna to the immigration officer: \"This is my first visit to England.\"     -> Lorna told the immigration ...................................................","answer":"officer that was her first visit to England.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Arthur: \"I hope to have time for reading next week.\"     -> Arthur said ....................................................","answer":"he hoped to have time for reading the following week","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"\"You are the most beautiful girl I have ever seen\" - he told me.     -> He told me ..................................................................","answer":"I was the most beautiful girl he had ever seen.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Nick: \"I'm going to visit my parents next month.\"     -> Nick declared that........................................","answer":"he was going to visit his parents the following month.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Linda and Terry: \"We can't come to the party next Saturday.\"     -> Linda and Terry said ....................................................","answer":"they couldn't come to the party the following Saturday.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Lilly: \"My parents are fine and I really get on with them.\"     -> Lilly told me ...................................................","answer":"her parents were fine and she really got on with them","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Gloria: \"I am sorry but I can't come to your birthday party because I'm going away for the weekend.\"      -> Gloria explained to me that...........................................................","answer":"she couldn't come to my birthday party because she was going away for that weekend","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"}]}